https://donner-kabab.github.io/portfolio/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/emma--donley/

## Skills & Tools

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Git
- Android Studio
- UI/UX design
- Microsoft Suit
- React
- Tableau
- Salesforce

#### **Education**

Certificate Web Development 2023-2024

#### CareerFoundry, online

Intensive project-based training program focused on JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and prominent libraries, frameworks and tools with industry-leading mentors.

#### Languages:

English: Native

# EMMA DONLEY

# **Professional Summary**

A web developer that creates unique designs and memorable experiences. With extensive history with customers and visual designs. Making designs that customers will be attracted to with quality work and personalized experiences. Committed to collaborative work and reliability.

## **Projects**

## Meet App

Personal project, CareerFoundry, July 2024

- Developed a web application with serverless functions (AWS lambda) using React to display events from google calendar and implemented offline availability.
- Learned and followed test-driven-development approach and translated user stories into scenarios for testing.

#### Hello-World

O Personal project, CareerFoundry, August 2024

- Built a chat app for mobile devices using React Native
- App provides users with a chat interface and options to share images and location.
- App uses Google Firestore/Firebase to store messages, images, and authentication

# **Experience**

#### Vivint | Provo, Utah

O December 2024 - Current

Account Manager

- Created detailed records of daily activity through online customer database.
- · Stayed current on company offerings and industry trends.

#### Precoa | Orem, Utah

August 2023 - January 2024

Sales Development Representative

- Developed successful strategies for identifying and converting prospective clients to long-term customers
- Gained customer trust and confidence by demonstrating a compelling, persuasive, and composed professional demeanor.

## Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints | Rigby, Idaho

October 2022 - June 2023

Seminary Student Teacher

- Facilitated small group activities and one-on-one instruction to meet individual student needs
- Encouraged critical thinking and problem-solving skills to enable students to leave their comfort zone.